本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：老奶奶      校对：小路     时间轴：虫不知
特效：Will      后期：冰河       监制：蛐蛐
■
绝
命
毒
师
第二季
第四集
美国船长
Captain America.
-你好  兄弟  -你好  兄弟
- What's up, brother?  - Hey, bro.
这主意太蠢了
This is stupid.
你有更好的主意吗
You got a better idea?
好吧  无所谓了
Okay, fine. Whatever.
那我们什么时候
So when do we, you know?
暂时不动手
We don't, for now.
等一切安顿好了再开始制毒
No cooking until things settle down.
安顿
Settle down?
你不是说事情不会有变化吗
I thought you're the one that said nothing's changed.
听着  我让家人担惊受怕深受折磨
Look, I just put my family through an ordeal
他们才刚开始接受我的现状  明白吗
That they're just now starting to accept, okay?
我不能
I can't...
这个太贵了
Ah, that's too expensive.
听着  我离家超过20分钟
Look, I can't leave my house
我老婆就开始担心
For more than 20 minutes without my wife worrying.
我需要时间来改善我们的关系
I need time to mend fences.
你要改善关系  那我怎么办
So while you're fixing fences,what about me, huh?
你那个混蛋小舅子把我的钱都收走了
Your A-hole brother-in-law took all my money.
这里有600块
That's $600.
剩下的那些钱呢
What about the rest?
-什么  -你那一半钱都是我的
- Rest of what?  - Half your money's mine.
说好55分成的  这不是你的生意经吗
You know,50/50 partners.That's your business motto.
你这么说什么意思  你犯错  我买单吗
Meaning what, exactly?That I suffer for your carelessness?
是你想跟屠库合作
You're the one who wanted to work with Tuco.
要不是因为这个  就不会搞成这样
If it weren't for that, none of this would've happened.
稍后再谈  好吗
We'll talk about this later, okay?
目前就不要联系了  明白吗
As for now, no contact. Understood?
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
我先走
I leave first.
沃尔特
Walt!
在厨房呢
In the kitchen.
你怎么还动起了炉子
I didn't know you were allowed to touch the stove.
搞笑呢  葛罗卓[名小丑]
Hilarious, Groucho.
去吧  快坐下
Go on, grab a seat.
桌上有果汁
Juice is on the table.
-早上好  宝贝儿  -嗨  妈妈
- Good morning, honey.  - Hey, Mom.
老爸正做早饭呢
Dad's cooking breakfast.
放心  盘子我也由我来洗
But don't worry.I'm also doing all the dishes.
不错吧  跟我来
Nice? Follow me.
还有橙汁和葡萄柚汁
There's also orange juice and grapefruit juice,
虽然我并不喜欢喝这些
Which, personally, as you know, I've never been a fan of.
但是考虑到他们富含多酚
But considering all the polyphenols
还有纤维蛋白  对人体无害
And the albuminoids, can't hurt.
沃尔特  你不必这么做
Walt,You didn't have to do this.
-葡萄柚汁要吗  -好的  谢谢
- Grapefruit juice?  - Yes, please. Thanks.
好了  宝贝  你要吗
There you go. Honey?
我喝橙汁  谢谢
I'll stick with orange, thank you.
好了  开吃吧  开吃吧
All right. Dig in, dig in.
不然薄煎饼凉了
Pancakes are not getting hotter.
好吧  我知道了  斯蒂利·丹[乐队]
All right. Got one. Steely Dan.
-不是  -肯定是
- No.  - Yes, absolutely.
不  在纯音乐才能方面
No, in terms of pure musicianship,
他们比你知道的任何现代乐队都强
I would put them up against any current band you could name.
你压根不知道什么现代乐队
You wouldn't know any current bands.
-跑题了  -宝贝  祝你愉快
- That's besides the point.  - Have a good day, honey.
你也是
You too.
伯兹史卡斯  我想起一个
Boz Scaggs.There's another one.
管他们是谁呢
Whoever they are.
拜拜啦  谢谢你的早餐
Bye,thanks for breakfast.
不客气  让路易斯小心开车  知道吗
You're welcome. Tell Louis to drive carefully, will you?
好
All right.
我们儿子竟然没听说过伯兹史卡斯
Our son doesn't know who Boz Scaggs is.
我们做父母的真失败
We have failed as parents.
仔细想想  我也不知道伯兹史卡斯
Come to think of it, I barely know who Boz Scaggs is.
得了吧
Stop it.
把你的盘子给我  我来  我来
Give me your plate. I'll get it. I'll get it.
谢谢
Thank you.
听着
Hey, listen,
日历上标明
In the calendar section,
这一周
All week long,
在新墨西哥大学有个小说作者研讨会
There's a fiction writer's seminar at UNM.
讨论如何出版
And, you know, probably talking about how to get published
之类的事情
and that sort of thing.
总之  我以为你会去
You know, so, anyway, I thought maybe you might...
如果你去的话  我陪着你
I mean, I'll go with you if you like.
我还想了想的那晚你问我的事情
And I was thinking about what you asked me the other night.
你怀疑我还有一部手机
You know, you were wondering if I had a second cell phone.
我一直都在想这件事
And, well, I've been thinking about that a lot,
我觉得你听到的
And I think what you heard
是我设的手机闹铃
Was my cell phone alarm going off.
我之前一直用闹铃当做治疗提醒
I've been using it a lot as a medication reminder to...
提醒我吃药
Well, remind me to take my medication.
诡异的是
And the weird thing is that
闹铃的声音跟电话铃声
The alarm sound is almost exactly the same
一模一样
As the regular phone ring,
说起这一点  设计得真不人性化
Which is really a poor design, if you ask me.
事情可能就是这样的
But I think that was probably it.
我试过把铃声改掉
I tried to go in and change it to a different sound,
改成不同的声音  但是...
Other than the phone ring, but...
这些玩意儿太复杂了
They so overcomplicate these things.
总之
Anyway,
正好我也把手机弄丢了
It was probably just as well that I lost it.
市场上应该又有新型的手机了
There's got to be a new one on the market by now.
如果我们一起去新墨西哥大学的话
You know, if we do this thing at UNM,
回来的路上
Maybe on the way home,
我们可以顺道给我买部新手机
We can stop by,and I can get a new cell phone.
斯凯勒
Skyler
律师事务所
准备好了
Ready?
你能帮个屁忙啊
Yo, for what might help.
不会又是劝说会吧
Not another intervention.
杰西·布鲁斯·平克曼
Jesse Bruce Pinkman,
根据新墨西哥不动产法47章第8条第13项
Pursuant to Section 47-8-13 of the New Mexico Real Property Code,
现通知你搬出
You are hereby given notice to vacate
位于阿尔布开克市马歌路9809号  87104住所
The premises listed as 9809 Margo,Albuquerque,87104.
等等  什么
Wait. What?
你要把我从我自己房子赶出去
You're kicking me out of my own house?
是你姑妈琪妮的房子
It's your aunt Ginny's house.
-她送给我了  -杰西  她可没送给你
- She gave it to me.  - She never gavet to you, Jesse.
你只是享有居住权
You were allowed residentiary privileges.
你父母才是房屋所有权持有人
Your parents have always been the property owners.
听着  我们之前谈过  好吗
Look, we talked about this, okay?
我把房子卖了  五五分成
I'd sell the house, we'd split it 50/50.
都说好了  又他妈搞什么啊
That was the deal. What the hell happened?
问题是你在房子里制毒
What happened is you're a speed manufacturer.
不  我没有  什么
No, I'm not. What?
杰西  缉毒局的探员过来找过你
A DEA agent came looking for you, Jesse.
他找到我们家来了
He came to our front door.
好吧...
Okay...
实际上我一直在协助他们
Because I've actually been helping them,
告诉你们的话就会有太多麻烦
Which I could get into a lot of trouble for telling you,
你们不要谢我
So you're welcome.
我看过地下室
I saw your basement.
我有点担心
I was worried,
所以我过去看了看
So I went over there and I let myself in,
发现了你的实验室
And I found your laboratory.
你们竟然有钥匙
You guys have your own key?
生产二级管制药物
Manufacture of a Schedule II controlled substance
是二等重罪
Is a second-degree felony.
根据联邦财产冻结法
Under federal asset seizure,
政府有权没收你的房子
The government can take the entire house.
东西已经不在那里了
It's not even there anymore.
我都清理出去了
I cleaned it all out.
儿子  你想毁掉自己的一生  我们也没办法
Son, we can't stop you from ruining your life,
但你不能拖我们下水
But you will not drag us down with you.
72小时内搬出房子
Vacate the house in 72 hours.
否则  你父母授权我可以通知相关部门
Otherwise, your parents have authorized me to contact the authorities.
清楚了吗
Is that clear?
还有什么疑问吗
Do you have any questions for us?
3天时间  平克曼先生
Three days, Mr. Pinkman.
走吧
Come on.
我修好了车库门
I fixed the garage door.
很好
Great.
有个滑轨歪了  所以总跳
One track was bent.That's why it was bouncing.
-你今天去哪儿了  -出门
- Where were you today?  - Out.
你还好吧
Is everything okay?
是的  一切安好
Yeah,everything's fine.
我想那些癌症互助组还是很有用的
For what it's worth, I was thinking about going back to those meetings,
我会继续去的
The cancer support group.
那不错
I think that's good.
是的  很不错
Yeah, that's good.
钱的事  你说的没错
You were right on the money about that.
敞开心扉的交流
It's good to, you know...
还是不错的
Talk about things.
太好了
I think that's great.
你没接电话
You don't answer your phone?
是的  我只是
No, I've just been...
比较忙
Pretty busy.
你怎么
How'd you...
没错  你有钥匙
Oh, right, you have that key.
听着
Hey, listen.
我一直在想
So I've been thinking a lot about our...
我们那天的谈话
Conversation we had the other day,
我终于明白
And I completely get why
爸爸要那么鞭策我的原因了
Dad totally tweaked off on me like that and...
杰西  不只是你爸爸这么想
It's not just your father, Jesse.
我明白  明白
I know. I know.
我只想说
I'm just saying it's a really,
我醒悟了不少
really big wake-up call for me,
所以我想跟你谈谈
Which is why I wanted to talk to you.
事实上  我一直在考虑去商业学校念书的事
I've been thinking real seriously about business school, actually,
所有事情都可以在电脑上搞定
And you can do the whole thing from your computer now, and...
不  妈妈  这是件好事
No, Mom, Mom. Hey, this is good.
我们用心交流
You know, we're talking,
好好谈谈
Starting a dialogue.
杰西  一切都晚了
The time for talking has passed, Jesse.
搞什么啊
What the hell, yo?
我以为你们只是想提醒我
I thought it was just a wake-up call.
我们把这些都放在仓库
We are putting it in storage.
等你真正成熟了  可以要回去
When you decide to grow up, you can have it back.
你怎么不成熟点呢  妈妈
Why don't you grow up, Mom?
琪妮想我待在这里  我才是那个一直照顾她的人
Ginny wanted me here.I was the one who took care of her.
我带她去看医生  每天给她做午饭
I took her to her appointments and made her lunch every day.
这房子是我应得的
I earned this!
你并没有每天给她做午饭
You did not make her lunch every day.
你又做什么了呢
What did you do, huh?
她躺在那儿等死  你他妈在哪儿呢
She's lying there dying, and where the hell are you?
别跟我来劲
Don't start with me.
现在呢
Now what,
你狠心把你大儿子扫地出门
You've decided to, I don't know, make your eldest son homeless?
真是和谐家庭啊
Great family, Mom!
你为什么要这样
Why are you like this?
为什么
Why?
你有两串钥匙
You have two sets of keys
还有车库的锁
And the padlock to the garage.
走的时候放在厨房的柜子上
Leave them on the kitchen counter when you leave.
不要  妈妈
No, Mom! Mom!
我能去哪儿呢
Where am I supposed to go?
宝贝  我不知道
I don't know, sweetheart.
求你了
But please...
回头是岸啊
Turn your life around.
这么做就能帮上大忙了啊
This is gonna help big time with that.
贱人
Bitch!
靠
Jeez.
怀特先生
Oh, hey, Mr. White.
这才对  别坐在车里按喇叭
That's the way. Don't just sit out there honking.
进来打个招呼吧
Come in and say hello.
我做了煎蛋  你要来一个吗
We've got omelets. You want an omelet?
不了  谢谢
No, I'm good.
新墨西哥圣诞式  加了红辣椒还有青椒
New Mexican Christmas style, red and green chilies.
不了  谢谢
No. Thank you, though.
我和弗林该走了
Flynn and me gotta get going.
-弗林是谁  -弗林
- Who's Flynn?  - Flynn...
是你
He's your...
弗林
Flynn?
没错
Yeah
怎么了
So?
怎么了  没事
So? Nothing.
-准备好了吗  -我喜欢这个名字
- You ready?  - Like it.
拜  怀特先生
Bye, Mr. White.
再见
Bye!
弗林
Flynn?
你知道弗林是怎么回事吗
You know about this Flynn thing?
好吧  弗林
Ok, Flynn
难道是埃洛·弗林
As in what, Errol?
不知道  最近他都喜欢别人这么叫他
I don't know. It's what he likes to be called these days.
小沃尔特这名字怎么了
What's wrong with Walter Jr.?
别乱想了
Don't take it personally.
他只是想有自己的个性
He wants his own identity.
你觉得他跟路易斯说起过我吗
You think he told Louis about me?
-失忆的事情  -路易斯可是他朋友  沃尔特
- About the blackout?  - Louis is his friend, Walt,
你的失踪令他心烦不已
And your disappearance upset him.
我做了煎蛋
I made omelets.
我要出门  谢谢
I'm going out, but thanks, though.
你去哪儿
Where you going?
你能接下电话吗
Can you get the phone, please?
没问题
Yeah. Absolutely.
-怀特家  -是我  方便说话吗
- White residence.  - Yo, it's me. Is this a good time?
你不明白什么叫不要联系吗
What part of "no contact" didn't you understand?
-但是出了点岔子  -我不管  说好了的
- But there's a problem. - I don't care. We agreed.
有没有付费频道都对我们没有影响
No amount of pay-per-view channels is gonna make any difference.
宝贝  我们很满意现有的有线电视运营商吧
Honey, we're happy with our cable provider, right?
很满意
We're happy.
斯凯勒  斯凯勒
Skyler. Skyler.
你去哪儿  这个都不能告诉我吗
Where are you going? Can you at least tell me that?
出门
Out.
接电话去吧  沃尔特
Should probably get that, Walt.
几个小时后我就回来
I'll be back in a few hours.
斯凯勒
Skyler.
-怎么了  -我知道不该打电话
- What?  - Yo, I get I shouldn't call,
但我现在情况不妙  我需要钱
But I'm in a situation over here,and I need my money.
不是给过你600块了么
I just gave you $600.
是的  谢谢了  沃尔巴斯老爹[沃尔巴斯是个富豪]
Yeah, and thanks, Daddy Warbucks,
但是那时候我的房子
But that was before my housing situation
还没有出状况呢  明白吗
Went completely testicular on me, okay?
你把钱都拿去吸毒了  对吗
You smoked the entire 600,didn't you.
什么  没有
What? No!
没有
No.
听着  杰西  你的问题是你的问题
Look, Jesse,your problems are just that...your problems.
不要联系  别再打电话来
No contact. Do not call here ever.
时机成熟了  我会通知你
When the moment is right, I will call.
怀特先生  你没听明白
Mr. White, you're not listening!
他们要赶我出门
They're kicking me out of my house!
小畜生
You son of a bitch.
老畜生
Son of a bitch!
谢谢  非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢了  哥们  你落东西了
Thanks, man! Hey, guy! You forgot something!
你把冰格落了  冰格有用着呢
You forgot your ice trays! You're gonna need the ice trays!
这里落东西了  拿走
Forgot something here! Take this!
等一下  哥们
Hold on, buddy.
说真的  我们应该让"少女杀手"再出山
Yo, we should get Twot Hammer up and running again, yo. I'm serious.
听上去不错
I know. That sounded tight.
真的谢谢你  P
Hey, thanks again, P.
我让杀虫的那家伙尽快处理完毕
I made sure this stock knock exterminator put me on his speed dial.
最多两晚
Two nights tops.
你还住在马歌路上的姑妈家吗
You still staying at your aunt's on Margo?
是的  我打算搬出去  可能搬去诺布山
Yeah. I'm thinking of moving. Nob Hill, probably.
浪子杰西  追梦少年啊
Jesse-matic, living the dream.
好了  小鬼  听着
Okay, buddy, listen.
我们说好的  乖乖把胡萝卜吃了
You're gonna eat your carrots like we talked about right?
太烫了
Too hot.
不行  小鬼  记得吗
No, buddy. Remember?
来吧  是的
Come on. Yes.
听着  跟我讲讲
Listen, hey, talk to me, man.
你还在四处留情吗
Are you still having mad relations out there?
告诉我吧  我不讨厌花花公子
You can talk to me.I won't hate a player.
我不撒谎  我还是很万人迷的
I can't lie. It's pretty hectic out there female-wise.
靠  嫉妒死我了
Damn. I'm hating, man.
所以要让"杀手"再次出山  明白吗
See, that's why we need to get the Hammer up and running, you know?
-出去透透气  -肯定很潇洒
- Get you out of the house.  - How awesome would that be?
来吧  看  我也吃了
Come on. Look. What?
像你一样  我把绿色部分都切了
I cut all the green parts off like you...
-尽管吃  好吗  -我们应该这么干  明白吗
- Just eat them. Please?  - We should do this, you know?
找奇弗和安东尼一起风流
Track down Chivo and Anthony and demo up.
重回历史舞台
Get back in the scene.
抱歉  等一下  好吗
I'm sorry, man. Just hold on one second, all right?
好吧  听着  这样吧  你吃一口三明治
Okay, listen. How about you take a bite of your sandwich,
再吃一口
And then you take...
妈咪回来啦
Mommy's home!
-你好 -你好
- Hi!  - Hello!
宝贝  还记得杰西·平克曼吗
Hey, honey, you remember Jesse Pinkman?
他的房子闹虫灾
His house is getting bug bombed,
我答应让他住几晚
And I said he could crash a few nights.
你好 杰西
hi,jesse.
保罗  跟我到卧室把这些整理一下
Paul, could you help me in the bedroom with these?
好
Sure.
我小时候也不喜欢胡萝卜
I used to not like carrots, too.
本  该睡觉啦
Hey, Ben, I think it's someone's nap time.
过来
Come on.
哥们  你千万别生气
Man, dude, you're gonna kill me.
我竟然忘了这周末有亲戚要过来
I totally spaced that the in-laws are crashing this weekend.
你再联系其他人吧
You got other people to call?
没关系  我朋友多着呢
No, that's cool.I got tons of people.
亲戚
Yo, in-laws?
-P  你真倒霉  -是啊  我知道
- Sucks to be you, P.  - Yeah, I know, huh?
我来吧
Dude, here.
再见  哥们
See you, man.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
听着  我只住三四个晚上
Look, I'm asking to crash three, maybe four nights, and...
我问过猴子  所有人我都问过了
I already called Badger, all right? I called everyone.
我需要朋友的帮忙  哥们
I need a solid here, bro.
好吧  随你便吧
Yeah, whatever.
行  行  这样吧
All right. All right. How about this?
就今晚怎么样
What if it's just for tonight?
等等
Wait.
不  开什么国际玩笑
No, you cannot be serious.
不会这么倒霉吧
You cannot be serious!
有人把你摩托车偷走了
Someone took your bike, man.
你惨了
Not cool.
早
Morning.
妈妈去哪儿了
Where did mom go?
出门
Out.
早饭呢
Where's breakfast?
我们做点事吧
Let's go do something.
比如
Like what?
有趣的事
Something fun.
好了  准备好没  踩离合器
All right, ready? Let's put it in gear.
-脚放在  很好  -是的  放好了
- Is your foot on the... Okay. Good.  - Yeah. I got it.
好
Good.
稳一点  很好  就这样
Yes. Nice and smooth. Good. Just like that.
很好  手的位置抓得不错  很好
Good. I like the hands at 10 and 2. Very nice.
好了  慢一点
Okay, let's slow down here
减速准备左转
To a stop in preparation for a left-hand turn.
很好  轻点踩刹车
All right. You might want to...go easier on the brake.
-抱歉  -没关系  你做得很好
- Sorry about that.  - That's all right. You're doing fine.
-比上次好多了  -路易斯一直在帮我练习
- Much better than last time, huh?  - Louis has been helping me.
是吗
Has he?
很好  很好
Good. Good. Okay.
别忘了打方向灯  好
Don't forget the turn indic... Good.
我不说了  你知道该怎么做
I'll stop talking. You know what you're doing.
来个左转弯
And let's make that left-hand turn.
稳一点  很好
Nice and smooth. Very nice.
往右转
Right hand.
很好  很好
Good. Good. Okay.
-你两脚同时用  -是的
- Are you using both feet?  - Yeah.
不行  等等  你不能这么做
No. Wait. Wait. No, Walt. You can't do that.
你不能同时踩在两个踏板上
You can't use one foot on each pedal.
-为什么不行  -因为不可以  停车  沃尔特  明白吗
- Why not?  - Because you can't. Stop, Walt. Okay?
停车
Stop,pleaes.
-好  -爸爸  这样容易点
- All right.  - Dad, this is way easier.
听着  容易的方法不等于正确的方法
Come on,there's the easy way,and then there's the right way, right?
再试一次  只用右脚
So let's just try it again,right foot only.
-好吧  -好
- All right.  - Okay?
好了  你不必  很好  不错
Okay,just...You don't have to...Okay.All right.That's fine.
你  很好
Just... That's okay.
再试一次
Just try it again.
走吧
Here we go.
我们再试一次
Let's just...Just try it again.
慢一点
Go just a little easier.
好的  很好  好多了  看到没
Good. Great. That was better. See?
是吧  好多了  油门  刹车  油门  刹车
Right? Better? Right.The gas,the brake,the gas,the brake.
我做不了
I can't do this.
我的腿不好使
My legs don't work that way.
你的腿很好  只要坚持一下
Your legs are fine. You just have to stick with it.
别太约束自己  沃尔特
Don't set limits for yourself, Walt.
你很棒
You're all right.
我们能搞定
We'll get this.
我保证  我们再试一次吧  好吗
I promise.Now let's just try again. All right?
-好  -走吧
- All right.  - Here we go.
你不必  仅管往前开  很好  继续
Well,you don't need to...just take off, but all right, here we go.
慢一点
Slow it down just a little bit.
很好  前面转弯
All right, we have a turn coming up here,
准备踩刹车
So prepare to apply the brakes.
沃尔特  踩刹车  刹车  刹车
Prepare, Walt, for the brakes. The brakes, the brakes...
-我正刹着呢  -你又两只脚一起用了
- I'm braking!  - You're using both feet again.
-没停下来  -你踩的是油门  踩刹车  刹车
- It's not stopping.  - That's the gas. Use the brakes. Brake.
这么停车也行
That's one way to stop.
我说过
I told you.
弗林
Flynn.
举起手来  混蛋
Hands up, asshole!
老实点  不然崩了你
So help me, I will spread you.
不要  求你了  是我  杰西
No, please, no, all right? It's me, okay? It's Jesse.
好吗
All right?
这是我的房车  你拖过来的
Look, this is my RV. You towed it.
你表弟猴子  记得吗
Your cousin Badger, remember?
你来这干什么
What the hell you doing here?
臭死了你
You smell like shit.
说来话长
It's a long story.
我帮你把这破车修好了
So I fixed up your felonious rolling laboratory here.
花费750块
$750 for the repair.
加上厕所就是1000  你另外还欠我500
Make it a grand,counting the toilet,plus the $500 you already owe me,
付清后  你可以滚得远远的了
And you're good to drive on out of here to someplace far away,
滚蛋
Upwind.
事情是这样的
Here's the thing.
今天给不了钱
I can't pay you today.
但这周内可以给你  好吗
But I can pay you this week,all right?
1750块
$1,750?
就算是1750块吧  算上
We'll make it $1,750 for, like...
利息
Interest.
-我以为你说话算数呢  -当然
- I thought your word was your bond.  - It totally is.
只不过我现在手头没钱
Definitely. I just don't have the money at this particular moment.
很快就会有了
But I will, soon.
我是这么想的
Here's my counter-offer.
你滚出去  这些东西卖了钱抵债
I kick you out.I take payment from your inventory.
我认识一个人专门收这种破烂
I know a guy that'll pay premium for this kind of crap.
好吧  2000块
All right. 2 grand.
给我两天时间  2000块
Two days, 2 grand.
公平交易
That's totally fair.
别把我东西卖了
Just don't take my cook stuff.
好吗  我就剩这些家当了
All right? That's all I got left.
求你了  好吗  我真的
Please, all right? I really...
真的需要
God, I really need
缓一缓
A break here.
克洛维斯  拜托了
Clovis, come on.
不知道  里面有不少东西
I don't know.There's a bunch of stuff in there.
还有叫什么甲胺的东西
There's something called methylamine. Me... Meth...
管它叫什么呢  甲胺
However the hell you pronounce it. Methylamine.
不清楚  我掂量了下  应该是满的
I don't know. I banged on it.It sounds pretty full to me.
我靠  多少钱
Holy shit. How much?
路易斯载沃尔特上学去了
Louis took Walt to school.
我在想
I was thinking maybe...
我们可以趁机好好谈谈
This would be a good time to talk.
我曾梦见拥有一个古董修车铺
I dreamt that I owned an antique bicycle repair shop.
在爱尔兰
In Ireland.
奇怪
Weird.
是很奇怪
Sounds weird.
我想道歉
I wanted to apologize
为这一切
For everything.
我
My...
要求隐私  我
Desire for privacy. My...
喜怒无常
Emotional...
总不在家
Unavailability.
癌症不是所有事情的借口
Having cancer doesn't excuse all that.
我不是一个称职的丈夫
I haven't been a good partner to you,
为此
And for that...
我深表歉意
I'm very sorry.
我爱你
I love you.
我爱这个家
And I love this family.
我只是
And I just...
想确认一下
Want to make sure that...
我们没有疏远
We don't lose contact.
谢谢
Thank you.
我同意
I agree.
就这么多
Is that it?
老天
God.
你还想冷战都什么时候
God, how long are you going to do this?
-什么  -冷战
- Do what?  - This.
不跟我说话
Not talking to me.
成天出门  也不告诉我去哪儿
Going out all day and refusing to tell me where.
我肯定生我的气了
You are obviously angry with me about something,
所以说出来吧
So let's talk about it.
老天
God.
我感觉到你对我不满
I feel like you're upset with me
因为你认为
Because you think that...
我有事瞒着你
I'm... up to something.
-比如  -我不知道  斯凯勒
- Like what?  - I have no idea, Skyler.
什么  我有外遇
What, that I'm having an affair?
是这个吗  你这么认为吗
Is that it? Is that what you think?
所以你才问我
Is that why you asked me about the...
是不是还有部手机  因为你认为我不忠
Some other phone? Because you think that I'm being unfaithful?
不知道
I don't know.
那你问啊
So ask me.
为什么
Why?
-你会告诉我吗  -是  我会
- Would you even tell me?  - Yes. I would.
我当然会
Of course I would.
没有
And no.
我没有外遇  明白吗
I'm not. I'm not having an affair, okay?
我怎么才能证明给你看呢
Now, what do I do to prove that to you?
发毒誓  我对天发誓  我没有外遇
Swear an oath? My right hand to God.I'm not having an affair.
我知道了  沃尔特
I heard you, Walt.
你没有外遇
You're not having an affair.
恭喜
Congratulations.
知道吗  恭喜你  斯凯勒
No, you know what? Congratulations to you, Skyler.
干得好
Great job.
你搞什么  我该怎么做
What is this? What do I have to do?
我诚心跟你谈  你却
I'm trying to talk to you, and you
好  那谈吧  沃尔特
Okay, so talk, Walt!
说点沾边的吧  别尽扯废话
Shut up and say something that isn't complete bullshit.
你想知道该怎么做
You want to know what you have to do?
你就得告诉我到底发生了什么
You have to tell me what's really going on right now.
就今天
Today.
别找借口
No more excuses.
也别道歉  别来这些
No more apologies.No more of these...
最后的早餐
Obvious, desperate breakfasts.
你不想跟我疏远  沃尔特
You don't want to lose contact with me, Walt?
很好
Good.
那就告诉我
Then tell me.
现在
Now.
告诉你什么
Tell you what?
我不知道你想要我说什么
What is it you want me to tell you? I don't know.
我们还没谈完呢  斯凯勒
We're not done here,Skyler!
你知道我为这个家付出了什么吗
Do you know what I've done for this family?
我真的很抱歉
Yo, I'm really sorry, okay?
你搞什么
What is wrong with you?
怎么一身蓝
Why are you blue?
天哪
Jesus.
抱歉  先从
I'm sorry. Let's just say it starts...
我父母的贪得无厌开始说吧
with my parents being greedy kleptomaniac douche bags.
你真的这么蠢吗
Are you actually this stupid?
没有  听着  我知道不该这么做
No, look.I know this isn't a optimal...
你竟然开着这车找到我家  还停在这条道上
To come to my house and park on my street, driving this vehicle...
我想问一下  你是不是脑子让屁给崩了
What the hell is wrong with you? I'm really asking.
没事  我很抱歉  只是
Nothing. I'm sorry. I just
要是斯凯勒看到你了呢
What if Skyler had seen you?
那怎么办呢  到时怎么办呢  天才
What then? What was the plan then, genius?
-不知道  -知道你为什么不知道吗
- I don't know.  - You know why you don't know?
因为你不动脑子  这就是原因
Because you don't think. That's why.
你不动脑子  甚至不知道怎么用脑子
You don't think. You never figured out how to think.
我道过歉了  我只想要回我的那份钱
I said I was sorry. I just need my half of the money,
然后就走人
And I will go.
你的那份
Your half?
根本没有你的那份钱
There is no your half of the money.
那些都是我的钱  明白吗
There is only my all of it.Do you understand?
我凭什么为你的冒失买单
Why should I be penalized because of your sloppiness?
听着  这样就不行  好吗
Look, that is completely uncool, all right?
-说好五五分成的搭档嘛  -什么搭档
- We agreed, 50/50 partners.  - Partners in what?
你做了什么  我问问你
What exactly do you do here? I've been meaning to ask
因为一直都是我在制毒
Because I'm the producer, right?
我制毒  你不过是个瘾君子
I cook.But from what I can tell, you are just a drug addict.
可悲的瘾君子
You are a pathetic junkie,
愚蠢到连
Too stupid to understand
最简单的操作都不会
And follow simple rudimentary instructions.
笨到连
Too stupid to re...
动手吧
Do it.
尽量不要
Try not...
碰我家东西
to touch anything.
吃早饭吗
Want some breakfast?